Guide to the E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection circa 1855-1953
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Outdoor Recreation and Nature Scenes, circa 1890-1945; Series 6
  - Group standing in front of tent, circa 1900; P101:1189
  - Group standing in front of tent, circa 1900; P101:1190
  - House in woods, P101:1258
  - House on lake or river, circa 1910; P101:1260a
  - House overlooking waterfront, circa 1910; P101:0641b
  - Hunting party by house, P101:1259
  - Individual outside with saw, P101:0815
  - Interior view of camp tent, circa 1900; P101:1137
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1321
    1 photographic print; 2 acetate negatives
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1322
    1 photographic print; 1 acetate negative
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1323
    2 photographic print; 1 acetate negative
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1324
    3 photographic print; 1 acetate negative
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1325
    4 photographic prints; 1 acetate negative
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1326
  - Kueny Ranch, circa 1945; P101:1327
  - Lake and woods, P101:0931
  - Lake and woods, P101:0933
  - Lake scene, P101:0975
  - Lake surrounded by forest, circa 1900; P101:0991
  - Large bush, P101:1368
  - Little girl next to stream, circa 1910; P101:0818
  - Little girl next to stream, circa 1910; P101:0822
  - Log across stream, circa 1910; P101:0922
  - Looking down on the Rogue River about 1/2 mile below Whiskey Creek, August 7, 1939; P101:1307
  - Man and a labrador retriever, circa 1900; P101:1242
  - Man and woman holding fish caught, circa 1915; P101:0686b
  - Man and woman on ground at a picnic, circa 1900; P101:1251
  - Man chopping wood, circa 1910; P101:0649
  - Man in camp with tent, cookstove and wagon, circa 1900; P101:1166
  - Man laying in grass, P101:0819
  - Man standing in front of small cabin, circa 1900; P101:1223
  - Man standing on porch holding fish, circa 1910; P101:0694
  - Man with fishing pole outside tent, P101:1372
  - Man with shotgun and birds, P101:0074
  - Man with shotgun and birds, P101:0075
  - Maple leaves, P101:0004
  - Maple leaves, P101:0010
  - Mary's River [?], circa 1900; P101:0982
  - Mary's River [?], circa 1905; P101:1003
  - Marys River swamp, circa 1905; P101:0258
  - Men in camp, circa 1900; P101:1175
  - Men in camp, circa 1900; P101:1176
  - Men in camp, circa 1900; P101:1177
  - Men with catch of fish, circa 1900; P101:1168
  - Moss-covered trees, circa 1915; P101:0961
  - Mountain, circa 1910; P101:0954b
  - Mountain, circa 1910; P101:0969
  - Mountain and road, P101:1270
  - Mountain and trees, P101:0967
  - Mountain and trees, P101:0971
  - Mountain cabin, P101:1043
  - Mountain camp, circa 1900; P101:1162
  - Mountain campsite, circa 1900; P101:1142
  - Mountain campsite, P101:1140
  - Mountain campsite, P101:1141
  - Mountain field, circa 1900; P101:0958
  - Mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0980
  - Mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0986
  - Mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0988
  - Mountain lake, P101:1018
  - Mountain lake, P101:1019
  - Mountain lake, P101:1025
  - Mountain sheep, circa 1890; P101:1100
  - Mountain stream reflecting pool, circa 1900; P101:0974b
  - Mountain view, circa 1920; P101:0993
  - Mountain view, circa 1920; P101:0994
  - Mountain view, circa 1920; P101:0997
  - Mountain, forest in foreground, circa 1900; P101:0992
  - Mountain, lake, and forest, circa 1900; P101:0968
  - Mountains scene, circa 1910; P101:0963
  - Mountains scene, circa 1910; P101:0964
  - Mountains scene, circa 1910; P101:0965
  - Mounted deer head, circa 1900; P101:0027
  - Mounted deer head, circa 1900; P101:0028
  - Pen and ink sketch of camp, Big Creek, Yaquina Bay, August 15, 1890; P101:1366
    1 non-photographic print
  - People in canoe, P101:1127
  - People in rowboat on river, circa 1900; P101:1201a
  - People in rowboat on river, circa 1900; P101:1201b
  - People standing among trees, P101:0972
  - People standing among trees, P101:0973
  - Perched pheasants, P101:0061
  - Perched pheasants, P101:0063
  - Pheasant, P101:0054
  - Pheasant, P101:0055
  - Pheasant, P101:0056
  - Pheasant, P101:0057
  - Pheasant, P101:0058a
  - Pheasant, P101:0058b
  - Pheasant, P101:0067
  - Pheasant, P101:0076
  - Pheasant, P101:0077
  - Pheasant, P101:0078
  - Pheasant and dog in a field, Corvallis, Oregon [?], circa 1910; P101:0853
  - Pheasant dog, P101:0065
  - Pheasant hen, P101:0047
  - Pheasant hen, P101:0048
  - Pheasant hen, P101:0049
  - Pheasant rooster, P101:0051
  - Pheasants, P101:0045
  - Pheasants, P101:0046
  - Pheasants, P101:0052
  - Pheasants and a dog, P101:0068
  - Pheasants and shotgun, P101:0073
  - Pheasants by cedar tree, P101:0060
  - Pheasants in a pen, P101:0059a
  - Pheasants in a pen, P101:0059b
  - Pheasants in a pen, P101:0064
  - Pheasants in a pen, P101:0066
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0039
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0040
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0041
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0042
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0043
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0044
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0036
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, circa 1905; P101:0037
  - Pheasants mounted on wall, P101:0062
  - Pheasants with hunting dog, P101:0038
  - Pheasant eggs, P101:0050
  - Picnic group, circa 1900; P101:0790
  - Picnic group, circa 1900; P101:1192
  - Picnic group, circa 1915; P101:0687a
  - Picnic group with bicycles in background, circa 1900; P101:0829
    Digitized photograph available in Oregon Digital.
  - Raft on mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:1145
  - Raft on mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:1217
  - Reflection of trees in mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0985
  - Reflection of trees in mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0990
  - River and woods, P101:0930
  - River or lake at dusk [?], circa 1905; P101:1002
  - River or lake at dusk [?], circa 1905; P101:1012
  - River or lake at dusk [?], circa 1905; P101:1020
  - Rose Wilson and others in camp, circa 1895; P101:1298
  - Rose Wilson and others in camp, circa 1895; P101:1299
  - Row boat on mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:1146
  - Rowboat on mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:1218
  - Rowboat on mountain lake, circa 1910; P101:1216
  - Scenic views of Eastern Oregon [?], circa 1920; P101:0601
  - Scenic views of Eastern Oregon [?], circa 1920; P101:0602
  - Scenic views of Eastern Oregon [?], circa 1920; P101:0603
  - Scenic views of Eastern Oregon [?], circa 1920; P101:0604
  - Scenic views of Eastern Oregon [?], circa 1920; P101:0605
  - Scenic views with elk, circa 1920; P101:0606
  - Scenic views with elk, circa 1921; P101:0607
  - Scenic views with elk, circa 1922; P101:0608
  - Sheep, Eastern Oregon, circa 1930; P101:0455
  - Small girl sitting on rocks, circa 1910; P101:0698
  - Small trees, circa 1900; P101:0983
  - Sodaville Springs, P101:257
  - Thortons, Shearers, Gerrys and Fullbrights at picnic near orchard, circa 1900; P101:0476
  - Three fishermen near Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1060
  - Three men at a fishing camp, circa 1900; P101:0784
  - Three men at a fishing camp, circa 1900; P101:1183
  - Three men with fish, circa 1930; P101:1049
  - Three men with fish, circa 1930; P101:1050
  - Three pheasants, P101:0069
  - Timber road, P101:0259
  - Tree, circa 1910; P101:0919
  - Tree with signs on it next to road, Mary's Peak in background, circa 1910; P101:0916
  - Trees along Mary's River [?], circa 1900; P101:0957
  - Trees along short of mountain lake, circa 1900; P101:0904
  - Trees and mountain, P101:1042
  - Trees by a stream, P101:1369
  - Trees by a stream, P101:1370
  - Trees in mountains after a forest fire [?], circa 1900; P101:0987
  - Trees in mountains after a forest fire [?], circa 1900; P101:0989
  - Two boats in front of houses, P101:1260d
  - Two fish, P101:0020
  - Two fish, P101:0021
  - Two fish, P101:0023
  - Two fish, P101:0024
  - Two fish, P101:0025
  - Two hunters with dogs and birds, circa 1883; P101:1237
  - Two pheasants, P101:0070
  - Two pheasants, P101:0071
  - Two pheasants, P101:0072
  - Two steelhead, P101:0019
  - Two women holding picnic baskets, circa 1910; P101:0650
  - Two women sitting among ferns in the woods, circa 1910; P101:1170
  - Two women sitting on ground in woods, circa 1900; P101:1221
  - Two women standing on rocks below cliff, circa 1900; P101:0879
  - Two women walking in the woods, circa 1910; P101:1171
  - Two women with picnic baskets, circa 1910; P101:1253
  - Unidentified cabin, circa 1915; P101:0934
  - Unidentified cabin, circa 1915; P101:0935
  - Unidentified cabin, circa 1915; P101:0936
  - Unidentified cabin, circa 1915; P101:0937
  - Unidentified cabin in the woods, P101:1206
  - Unidentified coast and mountain scene, P101:0926
  - Unidentified lake, circa 1900; P101:1009
  - Unidentified lake, circa 1900; P101:1010
  - Unidentified lake, circa 1900; P101:1011
  - Unidentified lake, P101:1005
  - Unidentified lake, P101:1006
  - Unidentified lake, P101:1007
  - Unidentified mountain and lake scene, P101:0923
  - Unidentified mountain scene, P101:0920
  - Unidentified mountain scene, P101:0925
  - Unidentified mountain view, P101:0277
  - Unidentified mountain view, P101:0278
  - Unidentified river, circa 1900; P101:1008
  - Unidentified river, circa 1910; P101:1013
  - Unidentified river, circa 1910; P101:1016
  - Unidentified river, circa 1910; P101:1021
  - Unidentified river, P101:1023
    1 photographic print (hand-colored)
  - Unidentified river or bay, circa 1900; P101:1014
  - Unidentified river or bay, P101:1022
  - Unidentified river or bay with clearcut hillside in background, P101:1017
  - Unidentified woods scenes, circa 1910; P101:0909
  - Unidentified woods scenes, circa 1910; P101:0910
  - Unidentified woods scenes, circa 1910; P101:0911
  - View of Benton Mine near Whiskey Creek, Jackson County, Oregon while on river trip, August 7, 1939; P101:1302
  - View of cabin on mountain lake, circa 1910; P101:1090b
  - View of camp, circa 1890; P101:0451b
  - View of Diamond Lake area, circa 1930; P101:1062
  - View of Diamond Lake area, circa 1930; P101:1063
  - View of Diamond Lake area, circa 1930; P101:1064
  - View of Diamond Lake area, circa 1930; P101:1065
  - View of Diamond Lake area, circa 1930; P101:1066
  - View of forest camp from river bed, circa 1900; P101:1138
  - View of mountain with trees in foreground, circa 1900; P101:0970
  - Views of mountain lake [?], circa 1910; P101:1209
  - Waterfall, P101:0276
  - Willamette River [?], circa 1900; P101:0928
  - Willamette River flood waters, circa 1900; P101:0597
  - Willamette River flood waters, circa 1900; P101:0598
  - Wilson, E.E. and others in a rowboat, circa 1900; P101:1149
  - Wilson, E.E. on rowboat in the Willamette River, circa 1900; P101:1219
  - Wilson, E.E. standing next to a boat underneath a bridge, P101:0415
  - Wilson, E.E., in canoe with others, circa 1910; P101:0387
  - Wilson, E.E., and others in camp, circa 1900; P101:1159
  - Wilson, E.E., and others in camp, July 19, 1897; P101:1153
  - Wilson, E.E., and others in camp sitting in front of large tree, circa 1900; P101:1154
  - Wilson, E.E., and others in camp sitting in front of large tree, circa 1900; P101:1155
  - Wilson, E.E., and others on a picnic, circa 1895; P101:0796
  - Wilson, E.E., and two others sitting by tent, circa 1900; P101:1156
  - Wilson, E.E., and two others sitting by tent, circa 1900; P101:1157
  - Wilson, E.E., and two others sitting by tent, circa 1900; P101:1158
  - Wilson, E.E., and unidentified individual sitting in front of tree with rifles, circa 1900; P101:0414
  - Wilson, E.E., back from a pheasant hunt, circa 1900; P101:0849
  - Wilson, E.E., feeding chicken, circa 1915; P101:0391
  - Wilson, E.E., fishing, circa 1910; P101:0392
  - Wilson, E.E., fishing, circa 1910; P101:0393a
  - Wilson, E.E., fishing in stream, circa 1900; P101:1148
  - Wilson, E.E., hunting, P101:0809
  - Wilson, E.E., hunting, P101:0810
  - Wilson, E.E., in tent, P101:1152
  - Wilson, E.E., meditating by a creek, circa 1900; P101:0854
  - Wilson, E.E., on picnic with friends, circa 1900; P101:0450
  - Wilson, E.E., Rose Wilson, Otto Wells, and Mrs. "Red" Wells at camp, circa 1890; P101:0451a
  - Wilson, E.E., sitting at camp table pouring coffee, circa 1900; P101:1165
  - Wilson, E.E., standing by stream, circa 1900; P101:1147
  - Wilson, E.E., standing by stream, circa 1900; P101:1160
  - Wilson, E.E., with hunters and catch in front of car, 1912; P101:1260b
  - Wilson, E.E., with hunting dog and pheasants, P101:0386
  - Wilson, E.E., with two deer after a hunt, circa 1900; P101:1164
  - Wilson, Lewis and Rose picnicking with others, circa 1910; P101:1231
  - Wilson, Lewis and Rose picnicking with others, circa 1910; P101:1232
  - Woman fishing in stream, August 9, 1897; P101:1224
  - Woman fishing next to pond, circa 1910; P101:0816
  - Woman holding fishing rod, circa 1910; P101:0706
  - Woman in boat holding fishing rod, circa 1910; P101:0707
  - Woman sitting in the forest, July 18, 1897; P101:0745
  - Woman sitting on large log, circa 1900; P101:1220
  - Woman sitting on log bridge in forest, circa 1900; P101:0966
  - Woman standing on path next to ferns, circa 1900; P101:1222
  - Woman standing on tree stump, P101:1112a
  - Woman with two children on bank of river, circa 1915; P101:1260c
  - Women washing and drying dishes at camp kitchen, P101:1182
  - Yellowstone National Park, circa 1920; P101:0233
  - Yellowstone National Park, circa 1920; P101:0236
  - Yellowstone National Park--Bridge across river, circa 1920; P101:0227
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0239
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0221
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0230
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0231
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0232
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0237
  - Yellowstone National Park--Geysers, circa 1920; P101:0238
  - Yellowstone National Park--Reservoir behind dam, circa 1920; P101:0224
  - Yellowstone National Park--River, circa 1920; P101:0220
  - Yellowstone National Park--River canyon, circa 1920; P101:0226
  - Yellowstone National Park--River rapids, circa 1920; P101:0222
  - Yellowstone National Park--River rapids, circa 1920; P101:0223
  - Wilson, E.E. and Percy Locey with saw on Mary's Peak Trek, 1946; P101:0447
  - Yellowstone National Park--River rapids, circa 1920; P101:0240
  - Yellowstone National Park--View of mountains, circa 1920; P101:0225
  - Yellowstone National Park--View of mountains, circa 1920; P101:0228
  - Yellowstone National Park--View of mountains, circa 1920; P101:0229
  - Yellowstone National Park--Waterfall, circa 1920; P101:0218
  - Yellowstone National Park--Waterfall, circa 1920; P101:0219
- People, circa 1855-1953; Series 7
  Series 7 is comprised of both candid and studio photographs of identified and unidentified individuals. Many of the photographs in this series are of E.E. Wilson and other Wilson family members. The series also includes images of Wilsons' friends and colleagues.
  - Abbey, E.A., circa 1870; P101:1329
  - Asquith, Nancy (Siletz Indian), 1910; P101:0453c
  - Baby buggy with child, P101:0837
  - Banquet in honor of E.E. Wilson, circa 1953; P101:0488
  - Boy in E.E. Wilson's law office, circa 1900; P101:1235
  - Boy riding in cart pulled by dog, circa 1910; P101:0838a
  - Boy riding in cart pulled by dog, circa 1910; P101:0838b
  - Bryson, Ed, circa 1895; P101:0482
  - Bryson, Ed, P101:0509
  - Bryson, John R., P101:0474a
  - Bryson, Mary St. Clair, P101:0474b
  - Child standing outside, P101:1198
  - Chittenden, A. (wife of), circa 1878; P101:0575
  - Copson, Godfrey V. [?] in garden, circa 1940; P101:0434
  - Copson, Godfrey V. [?] in garden, circa 1940; P101:0435
  - Copson, Godfrey V. [?] in garden, circa 1940; P101:0436
  - Copson, Godfrey V. [?] in garden, circa 1940; P101:0437
  - Copson, Godfrey V. [?] in garden, circa 1940; P101:0438
  - Couple in automobile, circa 1915; P101:1252b
  - Custer, Susie, P101:1330
  - Davidson, Crilla, 1895; P101:0420
  - Davidson, Crilla, 1895; P101:0421
  - Davidson, Crilla, circa 1900; P101:0419
  - Davidson, William Clinton, circa 1910; P101:0467
  - Doolittle, Arthur, P101:1331
  - Edgecomb, Ruby, standing by building, 1924; P101:0801a
  - Edgecomb, Ruby, standing by building, 1924; P101:0801b
    Digitzed image available in Oregon Digital.
  - Edgecomb, Rex E., 1924; P101:0802
  - Family gathering, circa 1880s; P101:0642
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, circa 1858; P101:0567a
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, circa 1860; P101:0567b
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, July 22, 1880; P101:0574a
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1858; P101:0333
    1 ambrotype
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1860; P101:0324
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1860; P101:0330
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1860; P101:0331
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1860; P101:0334
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1860; P101:0335
    1 tintype
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1890; P101:0325
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1905; P101:0328
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?], circa 1905; P101:0329
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?] with J. Auguste and Eliza Knight, circa 1870; P101:0326
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight [?] with J. Auguste and Eliza Knight, circa 1870; P101:0327
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight and Henry, circa 1905; P101:0342a
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight and Henry, P101:0343b
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight and son, circa 1905; P101:0341
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, and Eliza Knight [?], circa 1855; P101:0343a
    1 daguerreotype
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, Henry and son, circa 1895; P101:0345
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, Henry, son, and unidentified individual, circa 1900; P101:0346
  - Fitzpatrick, Alma Knight, wedding photograph, circa 1890; P101:0574b
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, circa 1890; P101:0340a
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, circa 1890; P101:0344
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, circa 1895; P101:0339
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, circa 1900; P101:0338
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, circa 1905; P101:0340b
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, and mother [?], circa 1895; P101:0342b
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, in sailor uniform with boat, circa 1895; P101:0336
  - Fitzpatrick, Henry, in sailor uniform with boat, circa 1895; P101:0337
  - Five men wearing hats on porch of house, circa 1900; P101:0657
  - Five people sitting on porch, circa 1900; P101:0688
  - Four women sitting on a porch, circa 1900; P101:1249
  - Four women sitting on steps of house, circa 1900; P101:0658
  - Fox, A. J., 1866; P101:0573
  - Fuller, Clemmie, P101:1332
  - Fuller, Mr. and Mrs., P101:1333
  - Girl wearing a basket on her head, circa 1910; P101:0644
  - Girl with head poked through newspaper, P101:0491
  - Graham, Mary, Rose Russell, Farnie Irvin, and Mattie Graham, circa 1870; P101:0462a
  - Graham, Mary, Rose Russell, Farnie Irvin, and Mattie Graham, circa 1870; P101:0462b
  - Group in automobile, circa 1915; P101:1252a
  - Group of people sitting on wooden platform, circa 1900; P101:0686a
  - Group of women sitting on railroad tracks, P101:0831
  - Group peering from behind tree, circa 1900; P101:1173
  - Group picnicking., P101:0619a
  - Group picnicking., P101:0619b
  - Group sitting on steps near sawmill, circa 1910; P101:0826
  - Group sitting on steps of a house in Corvallis, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1250
  - Group sitting on wood boxes, circa 1910; P101:0833
  - Group standing beneath large tree, circa 1900; P101:1245
    1 photographic print (cyanotype)
  - Group standing in front of Wilson family home, circa 1900; P101:1246
  - Group standing on boardwalk [?], circa 1900; P101:1208
  - Horner, John B. and Mrs., 50th Anniversary, P101:0320
  - Horses and carriage with people, circa 1900; P101:1278
  - Humphrey, Esther W., circa 1910; P101:0319
  - Humphrey, Esther W., circa 1900; P101:0318
  - Ink and watercolor portrait of unidentified girl, circa 1880; P101:0780
  - Johnson, "Uncle Joe" and Emma, circa 1910; P101:0468
  - Johnson, Doc with unidentified individual beside car, circa 1910; P101:0483
  - Johnson, William T., P101:0472
  - Knight, Alma, circa 1860; P101:0803
  - Knight, Alma, circa 1880; P101:0781
  - Knight, Alma [?], circa 1865; P101:0775
  - Knight, Alma and mother, circa 1860; P101:0799
  - Knight, Eliza [?], circa 1855; P101:0332
  - Laurence, Erma [?] with umbrella in college greenhouse, circa 1895; P101:0717
  - Lipscomb, Mr., P101:1335
  - Little girl pulling child in a wagon, circa 1900; P101:0664
  - Lnagel, Arthur, P101:1334
  - Louis, Leon, P101:0321
  - Man and woman on steps of house, circa 1911; P101:1252c
  - Man holding dog and man holding baby, standing on porch of house, circa 1900; P101:0655
  - Man in plaid jacket standing in front of barn, circa 1915; P101:0692
  - Man in rocking chair, P101:0691
  - Man lifting woman sitting in wheelbarrow, circa 1900; P101:0497
  - Man sitting at desk, circa 1890; P101:0762
  - Man sitting in wicker chair, circa 1910; P101:0699
  - Man sitting on porch, circa 1910; P101:0693
  - Man with baby on steps of house, circa 1900; P101:0661
  - Man with baby on steps of house, circa 1900; P101:0662
  - Master Prince (dog belonging to John S. Thornton or Johny Williams [?], P101:1365
  - McConnell, Mary, P101:1336
  - Merryman, Art, Margaret, and Eva and Ed Herald in goat cart, circa 1910; P101:1282
  - Mirtin, Mary, P101:1337
  - Native American child in cradleboard, circa 1900; P101:0681
  - Native Americans, one in cradleboard, circa 1900; P101:0679
  - Nesbit, Maude, 1872; P101:0800
  - Noltner, Anthony, circa 1865; P101:0572
  - Nun, P101:0761
  - One child pushing another in a wheelbarrow, P101:1371
  - People on back porch, woman with dustpan, circa 1910; P101:0832
  - People on deck of "Pomona" (steamboat), circa 1900; P101:1279
  - People sitting next to wood house, circa 1910; P101:1087a
  - Phipps, James B., circa 1865; P101:0571a
  - Phipps, James B., circa 1865; P101:0571b
  - Pratt, Annie A., circa 1890; P101:0316
  - Randle, Mr., P101:1338
  - Rounds, Charles, P101:1346
  - Rounds, Emma, P101:1342
  - Rounds, Frank [?], P101:1348
  - Rounds, Hesekiah, P101:1347
  - Rounds, Johny, P101:1344
  - Rounds, Johny, P101:1345
  - Rounds, Mary, P101:1343
  - Rounds, Rebecca, P101:1341
  - Rounds, Rebecca, Frank, and Johny, P101:1349
  - Rounds, Rodney, P101:1339
  - Rounds, Rodney, P101:1340
  - Rounds, Wallace, circa 1900; P101:0317
  - Russell, Rose, P101:1358
  - Ryckman, Matt L., circa 1930; P101:0315
  - Shearer, Earl, circa 1920; P101:0440
  - Shearer, Earl (daughter of), circa 1910; P101:0469
  - Shearer, John (wife of), and John Shearer, Jr., circa 1930; P101:0441
  - Shearer, Mahala A. Russell, and sons, circa 1885; P101:0439b
  - Shearer, Mahala A. Russell, and sons, circa 1900; P101:0439a
  - Sheuquist, R.S., circa 1905; P101:0471
  - Siletz Indian [?] child in papoose, 1910; P101:0453b
  - Siletz Indian [?] man, 1910; P101:0453a
  - Siletz Indian [?] woman, circa 1900; P101:0454a
    5 photographic prints; 1 5x7 glass negative
  - Siletz Indian [?] woman, circa 1900; P101:0454b
    5 photographic prints
  - Six people sitting on porch, circa 1900; P101:0660
  - Small boy eating a piece of fruit, circa 1900; P101:0697
  - Small boy sitting in yard with toy boats, circa 1900; P101:0703
  - Small child standing in wagon, circa 1900; P101:0671
  - Small child standing next to wagon, circa 1900; P101:0672
  - Small girl holding cat sitting in yard, circa 1900; P101:0678
  - Small girl standing in yard, P101:0704
  - Small girl standing next to trellised vines, circa 1900; P101:0669
  - Staats, Mrs., P101:1350
  - Studio photograph of woman, P101:0701
  - Thornton, John S., P101:1351
  - Thornton, John S., P101:1352